<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oscar Acevedo</title>
    <link>https://oscaracevedo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oscar Acevedo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://oscaracevedo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>안녕하세요</title>
      <link>https://oscaracevedo.com/kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oscaracevedo.com/kr/</guid>
      <description>제 이름이 Oscar이에요, 2018년 연세대학교에서 서울에 있는 외국인 유학생이었습니다.
지금 한국어 공부하고 있어는데 잘 못해요.
잘 부탁해요.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A brief description of my thesis that I&#39;m writing.</title>
      <link>https://oscaracevedo.com/blog/2019-5-30-my-thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oscaracevedo.com/blog/2019-5-30-my-thesis/</guid>
      <description>My thesis is about designing a Generative Adversarial Network architecture for compositional data.
Compositional Data Compositional data is noteworthy because of this kind of data occurs in different contexts. Mathematically, compositional data is represented by points on a simplex , which means that given a point $$P_s(x_0,x_1,&amp;hellip;,x_n)$$ then $$\sum_{k=0}^{k=n} x_k = 1$$
Some examples of compositional data are:
 Molar concentrations in chemistry. Rock composition in geology. Soil composition. DNA sequencing data Microbiome data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://oscaracevedo.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oscaracevedo.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am recent graduate of UNAM&amp;rsquo;s Technology program at the Center for Applied Physics and Advanced Technology (Centro de Física Aplicada y Tecnología Avanzada). My degree program was multidisciplinary, focusing on science (chemistry and physics), and technology (computer science and electronics). Individually, my strongest areas are mathematics and coding, although I have microcontroller skills.
I am currently seeking a data-related internship or entry-level position. My goal is to have opportunities to bring data perspectives teams and help them make decisions that lead to success.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>